Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2014
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2014
Mus. Arc. 67
Haupt, Irene
3 CD-ROMs (180 digital images in tiff format)
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
Contains 180 digital images of musicians who participated in the June in Buffalo 2014 at the University at Buffalo, including guest composers Joshua Fineberg, Stephen Hartke, Philippe Hurel, Hilda Paredes, and Bernard Rands.
All files in the collection were renamed to reflect chronological sequence. Original filenames stated in the container list are transcribed as stated on the DVDs as received. Renamed files stored in the Institutional Repository.
Administrative Information
Terms of Access
Materials can be examined by qualified researchers in the Music Library during hours of operation during which Music Librarians are present. In order to insure access, researchers are advised to contact the Music Library in advance of visits.
Acquisition Information
Purchased from Irene Haupt, 2014.
Accruals and Additions
No further accruals are expected to this collection.
Alternate Forms
The entire collection of images from June in Buffalo 2014 is available in University at Buffalo Libraries Digital Collections.
Biographical Note
Irene Haupt, a graduate of the State University of New York at Buffalo, has been documenting the Buffalo arts scene through her photography since 1976. During that time she has worked for, or with, some of the most notable institutions in Buffalo, including the Irish Classical Theatre, Studio Arena Theater, the Kavinoky Theatre, the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra, the Theatre of Youth, the Albright-Knox Art Gallery, and the State University of New York at Buffalo. In addition to her specialty of theater photography, Irene Haupt has also devoted much of her career to the photography of musicians and musical events. Most notable is her documentation of the contemporary music scene in Buffalo, including coverage of the University at Buffalo's June in Buffalo festival of new music, 1982-1987, and 2000 to the present. Over the course of those years, she has created a visual record that contains images of some of the most significant composers and performers of the last quarter century. The list of names is impressive: Aaron Copland, Morton Feldman, Leo Smit, Virgil Thomson, Steve Reich, Ralph Shapey, Henry Brant, Earle Brown, Ursula Oppens, Jan Williams, Lukas Foss, Philip Glass, Otto Luening, Conlon Nancarrow, Ernst Krenek, Larry Austin, Lejaren Hiller, Elliott Carter, Milton Babbitt, John Cage, Charles Wuorinen, Jacob Druckman, and Yvar Mikhashoff, among others.
The June in Buffalo festival of contemporary music was begun at the University at Buffalo in 1975 by composer Morton Feldman. He directed the festival 1975-1978 and in 1980. The festival was dormant from 1981 through 1985. David Felder revived the festival in 1986 and has been its director since that time.
Scope and Content Note
The collection of Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2014 contains 180 digital images of participants in the festival for 2014. The list of musicians includes guest composers Joshua Fineberg, Stephen Hartke, Philippe Hurel, Hilda Paredes, and Bernard Rands. Performers include Irvine Arditti, Brad Lubman, Julia Bentley, Nicholas Isherwood, Steven Beck, Marianne Gythfeldt, Tom Kolor, Yuki Numata Resnick, Emi Ferguson, JoAnn Falletta, and Jerry Hou. Ensembles include Ensemble Court-Circuit, Signal Ensemble, Norrbotten NEO, the Slee Sinfonietta, and the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra.
Arrangement
One series arranged chronologically.
Container List
- Student composers Luciano Leite Barbosa and Marc Migo Cortes looking over scores during June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6663student composers JIB XXX.tif (Image-file jib2014_001)
- Composer Stephen Hartke with student composers Jessica Rudman, Camilo Mendez, and Luciano Leite Barbosa at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6665June in Buffalo XXX.tif (Image-file jib2014_002)
- Composer Stephen Hartke at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6669JIB Composer== XXX.tif (Image-file jib2014_003)
- Composer Stephen Hartke at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6673composer.tif (Image-file jib2014_004)
- Student composers Luciano Leite Barbosa, Chin Ting Chan, Mu-Xuan Lin, Paul Frucht, Binna Kim, John Rot, Haralabos Stafylakis, and Noah Meites at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: XXX_MG_6676student composers JIB 2014.tif (Image-file jib2014_005)
- Student composers Luciano Leite Barbosa, Chin Ting Chan, Noah Meites, Jessica Rudman, John Rot, Haralabos Stafylakis, Matt Sargent, and percussionist Trevor Saint at June in Buffalo 2014., 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6686student composers June in Buffalo 2014.tif (Image-file jib2014_006)
- Composer Joshua Fineberg preparing for a lecture at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: XXX_MG_6695composerXXX.tif (Image-file jib2014_007)
- Composers David Felder and Joshua Fineberg onstage before a lecture given by Fineberg at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6696composer lecture.tif (Image-file jib2014_008)
- Composer Joshua Fineberg and J.T. Rinker on stage before a lecture given by Joshua Fineberg at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6697composer Josuha Fineberg lecture.tif (Image-file jib2014_009)
- Composers David Felder and Joshua Fineberg at a lecture given by Joshua Fineberg at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6706.tif (Image-file jib2014_010)
- Student composers attending a lecture presentation by composer David Felder at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6714 Student composer and David Felder.tif (Image-file jib2014_011)
- Student composers, including Mu-Xuan Lin, Binna Kim, Haralabos Stafylakis, Matt Sargent, and Jessica Rudman at a lecture presented by composer David Felder at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: XXX_MG_6717student composersXXX.tif (Image-file jib2014_012)
- Composer Bernard Rands studying a score at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6722B Rands.tif (Image-file jib2014_013)
- Composer Bernard Rands in discussion with conductor Jerry Hou at a June in Buffalo 2014 rehearsal with Slee Sinfonietta members, violoncellist Jonathan Golove, percussionist John Bacon, and clarinetist Marianne Gythfeldt in the background, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6729Bernard Rands.tif (Image-file jib2014_014)
- Composer Bernard Rands in discussion with singer Julia Bentley at a rehearsal with Slee Sinfonietta members, violinist Yuki Numata Resnick and flutist Emi Ferguson at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6730rehearsal with Bernard Rands.tif (Image-file jib2014_015)
- Composer Bernard Rands in discussion with mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley at a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6734Bernard Rands Julia Bentley.tif (Image-file jib2014_016)
- Mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley conferring with percussionist Thomas Kolor in a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6739Julia Bentley Tom Kolor.tif (Image-file jib2014_017)
- Mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley conferring with percussionist Thomas Kolor in a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6740Juklia Bentley Tom Kolor.tif (Image-file jib2014_018)
- Mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley rehearsing with Slee Sinfonietta members, pianist Ning Yu, flutist Emi Ferguson, violinist Yuki Numata Resnick, and percussionist Thomas Kolor at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6743Rands rehearsal.tif (Image-file jib2014_019)
- Conductor Jerry Hou and mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley rehearsing with Slee Sinfonietta members, including percussionist John Bacon at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6745Rands rehearsal.tif (Image-file jib2014_020)
- Conductor Jerry Hou and mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley rehearsing with Slee Sinfonietta members, clarinetist Marianne Gythfeldt, violinist Yuki Numata Resnick, violoncellist Jonathan Golove, and percussionist John Bacon at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6752Rands rehearsal.tif (Image-file jib2014_021)
- Trumpeter Mike Gurfield with conductor Jerry Hou at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6756June in Buffalo 2014.tif (Image-file jib2014_022)
- Composers Bernard Rands and David Felder at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6760 Bernard Rands David Felder.tif (Image-file jib2014_023)
- Composer Hilda Paredes at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 black and white digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6772composer Hilda Paaredes-.tif (Image-file jib2014_024)
- Composer Hilda Paredes at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6772composer Hilda Paaredes---.tif (Image-file jib2014_025)
- Composer Hilda Paredes teaching a master class, with student composers John Rot, Ramteen Sazegari, Luciano Leite Barbosa, Marc Migo Cortes, Camilo Mendez (obscured), and John Yu at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6780composer Hilda Paredes master class.tif (Image-file jib2014_026)
- Composers Joshua Fineberg, David Felder, Bernard Rands and Stephen Hartke at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6788stage.tif (Image-file jib2014_027)
- Violinist Yuki Numata Resnick and pianist Steven Beck rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6790 Stephen Beck Yuki Numata Resnick.tif (Image-file jib2014_028)
- Composer Stephen Hartke in rehearsal with pianist Steven Beck and violinist Yuki Numata Resnick at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6796composer Stephen Hartke Yuki Numata Resnick pianist Beck.tif (Image-file jib2014_029)
- Flutist Emi Ferguson and percussionist Thomas Kolor (obscured) rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6799Emi Ferguson flute Tom Kolor percussion in Jessica Rudman .tif (Image-file jib2014_030)
- Student composers Jessica Rudman and Ramteen Sazegari at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6801student composers Jessica Rudman and Ramteen Sazegare.tif (Image-file jib2014_031)
- Student composers Jessica Rudman and Ramteen Sazegari with percussionist Thomas Kolor, flutist Emi Ferguson, and guitarist Sungmin Shin at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6804flutist Emi Ferguson, Tom Kolor percussion with student composer Jessica Rudman and Sungmin Shin, guitar.tif (Image-file jib2014_032)
- Composer Stephen Hartke teaching a master class to student composers Haralabos Stafylakis, and Mu-Xuan Lin at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6807master class comoiser Haertke.tif (Image-file jib2014_033)
- Composer Stephen Hartke teaching a master class to student composers Haralabos Stafylakis (obscured), and Mu-Xuan Lin at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6809composer Stephen Hartke master class.tif (Image-file jib2014_034)
- Horn player Adam Unsworth performing David Felder's composition Box man at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6812Adam Unswroth, horn in David Felder BoxMan.tif (Image-file jib2014_035)
- Clarinetist Adrián Sandí performing Hilda Paredes's composition Intermezzo Maliconico at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6813Adrian Sandi, clarinet.tif (Image-file jib2014_036)
- Flutist Emi Ferguson performing at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6816Emi Ferguson flute.tif (Image-file jib2014_037)
- Flutist Emi Ferguson performing at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6818 Emi Ferguson, flute.tif (Image-file jib2014_038)
- Clarinetist Marianne Gythfeldt performing Joshua Fineberg's composition Facets at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6819Marianne Gythfeldt, clarinet.tif (Image-file jib2014_039)
- Thomas Kolor performing Philippe Hurel's composition Loops IV on the marimba at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6820Tom Kolor.tif (Image-file jib2014_040)
- Violinist Yuki Numata Resnick and pianist Steven Beck performing Stephen Hartke's composition Netsuke at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Yuki Numata Resnick pianist Beck.tif (Image-file jib2014_041)
- Composer Bernard Rands at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6824Bernard Rands 2014.tif (Image-file jib2014_042)
- Conductor Jerry Hou conferring with mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley at a rehearsal with members of the Slee Sinfonietta, including violist David Rose at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6832Julia Bentley Jerry Hou conductor.tif (Image-file jib2014_043)
- Composer Bernard Rands listening to a rehearsal by conductor Jerry Hou, mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley, and members of the Slee Sinfonietta, percussionist Thomas Kolor, violist David Rose, and trumpeter Mike Gurfield at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6834 Julia Bentley Jerry Hou conductor Bernared Rands rehearsal.tif (Image-file jib2014_044)
- Composer Bernard Rands listening with Julia Bentley to a rehearsal by pianist Steven Beck at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6850pianist Beck.tif (Image-file jib2014_045)
- Composer Bernard Rands with mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley listening to a rehearsal by Steven Beck at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6852 June in Buffalo 2014.tif (Image-file jib2014_046)
- Composer Bernard Rands with conductor Jerry Hou and mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley listening to a rehearsal by Steven Beck at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6854pianist Beck with Bernard Rands reh..tif (Image-file jib2014_047)
- Pianist Steven Beck rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6868Steven Beck piano.tif (Image-file jib2014_048)
- Conductor Brad Lubman and student composer Marc Migo Cortes at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6876SEND SEND.tif (Image-file jib2014_049)
- Flutist Zach Sheets with student composer Luciano Leite Barbosa and pianist Oliver Hagen at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6879 June in Buffalo.tif (Image-file jib2014_050)
- Conductor Brad Lubman rehearsing with members of Ensemble Signal, violinist Yuki Numata Resnick, violoncellist Lauren Radnofsky, clarinetist Adrián Sandí, percussionist Nick Tolle, and flutist Zach Sheets at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6889 SEND SEND.tif (Image-file jib2014_051)
- Conductor Jerry Hou and mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley in performance with Slee Sinfonietta members, violinist Yuki Numata Resnick, flutist Emi Ferguson, violist David Rose, trumpeter Mike Gurfield, percussionist John Bacon, violoncellist Jonathan Golove (obscured), and clarinetist Marianne Gythfeldt at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6893 June in Buffalo.tif (Image-file jib2014_052)
- Mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley in performance with Slee Sinfonietta members, violinist Yuki Numata Resnick (obscured), pianist Ning Yu, flutist Emi Ferguson, and violist David Rose at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6895 Julia Bentley SEND SEND.tif (Image-file jib2014_053)
- Conductor Jerry Hou and mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley onstage after a performance with Slee Sinfonietta members, violinist Yuki Numata Resnick, pianist Ning Yu, flutist Emi Ferguson, violist David Rose, and trumpeter Mike Gurfield at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6896 Julia Bentley Jerry Hou conductor SEND SEND.tif (Image-file jib2014_054)
- Conductor Jerry Hou and mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley onstage after a performance with Slee Sinfonietta members, percussionist Thomas Kolor, violinist Yuki Numata Resnick, flutist Emi Ferguson, violist David Rose, trumpeter Mike Gurfield, violoncellist Jonathan Golove, percussionist John Bacon, and clarinetist Marianne Gythfeldt at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6897 Julia Bentley Jerry Hou conductor SEN SEND.tif (Image-file jib2014_055)
- Conductor Jerry Hou and mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley onstage after a performance with Slee Sinfonietta members, percussionist Thomas Kolor, violinist Yuki Numata Resnick, flutist Emi Ferguson, violist David Rose, trumpeter Mike Gurfield, violoncellist Jonathan Golove, percussionist John Bacon, and clarinetist Marianne Gythfeldt at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6898 Julia Bentley Jerry Hou conductor SENd SEND.tif (Image-file jib2014_056)
- Conductor Jerry Hou and mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley onstage after a performance with Slee Sinfonietta members, percussionist Thomas Kolor, violinist Yuki Numata Resnick, flutist Emi Ferguson, pianist Ning Yu, violist David Rose, trumpeter Mike Gurfield, violoncellist Jonathan Golove, percussionist John Bacon, and clarinetist Marianne Gythfeldt at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6899 Bernard Rands SEND SEND.tif (Image-file jib2014_057)
- Composer Bernard Rands and conductor Jerry Hou onstage with mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley and members of the Slee Sinfonietta, percussionist Thomas Kolor, violinist Yuki Numata Resnick, pianist Ning Yu, flutist Emi Ferguson, and violist David Rose after a performance at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6900Bernard Rands SEN SEND.tif (Image-file jib2014_058)
- Composer Bernard Rands and conductor Jerry Hou onstage with mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley and members of the Slee Sinfonietta, percussionist Thomas Kolor, violinist Yuki Numata Resnick, pianist Ning Yu, flutist Emi Ferguson, and violist David Rose after a performance at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6901Bernard Rands Send Send.tif (Image-file jib2014_059)
- Composer Bernard Rands and conductor Jerry Hou onstage with mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley and members of the Slee Sinfonietta, percussionist Thomas Kolor, violinist Yuki Numata Resnick, pianist Ning Yu, flutist Emi Ferguson, and violist David Rose after a performance at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6902Bernard Rands send send.tif (Image-file jib2014_060)
- Composer Bernard Rands and conductor Jerry Hou onstage with mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley and members of the Slee Sinfonietta, percussionist Thomas Kolor, violinist Yuki Numata Resnick, pianist Ning Yu (obscured), flutist Emi Ferguson, and violist David Rose (obscured) after a performance at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6903 Bernard Rands send send.tif (Image-file jib2014_061)
- Composer Bernard Rands and conductor Jerry Hou onstage with mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley and members of the Slee Sinfonietta, percussionist Thomas Kolor, violinist Yuki Numata Resnick, pianist Ning Yu, flutist Emi Ferguson, and violist David Rose (obscured) after a performance at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6904Bernard Rands Jerry Hou conductor.tif (Image-file jib2014_062)
- Composer Bernard Rands and conductor Jerry Hou onstage with mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley and members of the Slee Sinfonietta, percussionist Thomas Kolor, violinist Yuki Numata Resnick, pianist Ning Yu, flutist Emi Ferguson, and violist David Rose (obscured) after a performance at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6905 Bernard Rands send send.tif (Image-file jib2014_063)
- Composer Bernard Rands and conductor Jerry Hou with mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley and members of the Slee Sinfonietta, percussionist Thomas Kolor, violinist Yuki Numata Resnick, pianist Ning Yu (partially obscured), flutist Emi Ferguson, and violist David Rose at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6906 Bernard Rands.tif (Image-file jib2014_064)
- Pianist Steven Beck performing Bernard Rands's composition Piano preludes at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6910 Steven Beck piano.tif (Image-file jib2014_065)
- Composer Hilda Paredes in rehearsal with violinist Brusk Zanganeh at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6914composer Hilda Paredes.tif (Image-file jib2014_066)
- Composer Hilda Paredes in rehearsal with violoncellist Elemér Lavotha and violinist Brusk Zanganeh at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6915composer Hilda Paredes and Norrbotten NEO.tif (Image-file jib2014_067)
- Members of ensemble Norrbotten NEO, violinist Brusk Zanganeh, violoncellist Elemér Lavotha, flutist Sara Hammarström, and clarinetist Robert Ek rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6919Norrbotten Neo rehearsal.tif (Image-file jib2014_068)
- Conductor Petter Sundkvist in rehearsal with the ensemble Norrbotten NEO: percussionist Daniel Saur, flutist Sara Hammarström, violoncellist Elemér Lavotha, and violinist Brusk Zanganeh at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_692 Norrbotten NEO.tif (Image-file jib2014_069)